As John 5:24 says, "he who hears My Word and believes in Him who sent Me has everlasting life,
and shall not come into judgement, but has passed from death into life."
On Wednesday, the 21st of February 2018,
God's General, Evangelist Billy Graham, was promoted to glory at the good old age of 99.
The legacy of Evangelist Billy Graham, will live on forever in the hearts of believers worldwide,
and the countless thousands who came to the knowledge of saving grace through his ministry.
As Christians, our life is a race.
As ministers, our life is a warfare.
Like Apostle Paul, his warfare was accomplished, his race was run well, he has fought a good fight.
The course is good, the victory is sure.
As we celebrate the life and legacy of God's General, Evangelist Billy Graham,
let this moment prompt your hearts to make life's biggest decision as he did:
what to do with Jesus Christ.
You need not fear where you are going when you know Jesus is going with you.
Those who are born from above, long to be there.
Heaven is our home.
["Some day you will read or hear that Billy Graham is dead. Don't believe a word of it.
I shall be more alive than I am now. I will just have changed my address.
I will have gone into the presence of God."
- Billy Graham (1918 - 2018) - ]